<Modifier>
	<MainDesc>The element modifier will issue a single line with a  MODIFY command to the script. The script text can either automatically by defining the main attributes Mode, Modifier, Offset, DataWidth, XthFrame, XthFrameOffset, EndValue or StartValue. When either one of them is changed by the user a new DataText is being generated and a new FrameText. If just the DataText is changed then only a new FrameText will be issued without using the above mentioned main attributes.</MainDesc>
	<Comment>Comment that is added at the end of the script line with the separator „—„.</Comment>
	<Mode>Mode of the Modifier, can be SENDMODIFY or CHECKMODIFY.</Mode>
	<Modifier>Type of the modifier 2 digit hex value.  (usually 01). If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 2 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 2 digits. </Modifier>
	<Offset>Offset 4 digit hex value. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits. </Offset>
	<DataWidth>DataWidth 4 digit hex value. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits. </DataWidth>
	<XthFrame>XthFrame 4 digit hex value. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits. </XthFrame>
	<XthFrameOffset>XthFrameOffset 4 digit hex value. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits. </XthFrameOffset>
	<EndValue>EndValue 4 digit hex value. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits. </EndValue>
	<StartValue>StartValue 4 digit hex value. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits. </StartValue>
	<DataText>Final data that is added to the script. When modified here is will be persistent as long as none of the „main“ attributes of the element is change by the user.</DataText>
	<FrameText>Final script text of the modifier. If modified by hand it will be persistent as long as none of the above attributes has been changed by the user.</FrameText>
</Modifier>
