<CfgBlock>
	<MainDesc>This element is a child element of the DataBlock. But it is defined to generate directly a 9-2 configuration script for all phases. It gives you the possibility to define HighByte, LowByte and the Quality for each phase A,B,C and N. The quality can be put together with the attributes from the definition .</MainDesc>
	<DerivedType></DerivedType>
	<Comment>Comment that will be added in front of each script block being produced. But the comment is produced automatically at startup.</Comment>
	<NumberofDataBlocks>Number of blocks that will be produced. Changing this value will result in changing the number of values in the attributes cComment, Register and Data.</NumberofDataBlocks>
	<Register>6 digit hex value that defines the register of the Dionysos write command. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 6 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 6 digits. </Register>
	<Data>4 digit hex value that defines the data being written. If the attributes starts with an „h“, that value is interpreted as hex, (missing 0 will be added to a 4 digit value), if not the value is interpreted as decimal value and will be converted into a hex value with 4 digits.</Data>
	<FrameText>Final script test that is produced from above attributes. This test can be edited and will be saved with the element. As long as none of the main attributes is changed (Mode, Register, Date) it will preserve its value.</FrameText>
	<LowByte>LowByte of the 9-2 amplitude definition of the phases (0=A, 1=B, 2=C, 3=N)</LowByte>
	<HighByte>HighByte of the 9-2 amplitude definition of the phases (0=A, 1=B, 2=C, 3=N)</HighByte>
	<Quality>Quality defined from the below attributes.</Quality>
	<valitity>Valitity part of the quality. can be „valid“, „invalid“ or „questionable“</valitity>
	<overflow></overflow>
	<out_of_range></out_of_range>
	<bad_reference></bad_reference>
	<oscillatory></oscillatory>
	<failure></failure>
	<old_data></old_data>
	<inconsistent></inconsistent>
	<innacurate></innacurate>
	<source></source>
	<test></test>
	<operator_blocked></operator_blocked>
	<derived></derived>
</CfgBlock>
